- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
All: Aye, aye, Captain!
全体：是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
All: Aye, aye, Captain!
全体：是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Now, if nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 现在，如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ow!
全部：海绵宝宝！
- 噢！
All: SpongeBob!
全体：海绵宝宝！
- Come on!
- 快点！
All: SpongeBob!
- Everybody!
全体：海绵宝宝！
- 大家！
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
海绵宝宝！
♪ ♪
-
-  It's Patchy the pirate's
SpongeBob SquarePants Fan Club
- 这是海盗帕奇的
海绵宝宝粉丝俱乐部
Big Time Impressive Celebrity
Television Extravaganza,
大时代令人印象深刻的名人
电视盛宴，
with celebrity guests:
与明星嘉宾：
basketball mascot
The 3-Point Fowl,
篮球吉祥物
三分球鸟，
the guy on the penny,
那个拿着便士的家伙
Her Majesty the Queen,
女王陛下，
musical guest Pink,
音乐嘉宾粉红，
Sir Quentin and his little
wooden sidekick, Mr. Tinder,
昆汀爵士和他的小
木头助手，Tinder 先生，
and guest of honor,
SpongeBob SquarePants.
和主宾，
海绵宝宝。
From Encino, California,
来自加利福尼亚州恩西诺，
the president of the
SpongeBob SquarePants Fan Club
主席
海绵宝宝粉丝俱乐部
and your host,
Patchy the Pirate.
和你的主人，
帕奇海盗。
♪ Ten years... ♪
♪ 十年...♪
- Bawk! You're looking
at the wrong camera.
- 哇！你正在寻找
在错误的相机上。
- What? Potty?
Where are ya?
- 什么？便壶？
你在哪儿？
- Cue camera three.
- 提示摄像机三。
- I can't hear you!
- 我听不到你说话！
- Cue talent.
- 提示天赋。
- Cue?
What does that mean?
- 提示？
这意味着什么？
What are you pointing
at me for?
你指着什么
对我来说？
Do you have a headache?
你头痛吗？
Anyhoo, can you
believe it, kids?
无论如何，你可以吗
相信吗，孩子们？
It's been ten years
since I started
已经十年了
自从我开始
the SpongeBob SquarePants
Fan Club.
海绵宝宝
粉丝俱乐部。
And he's here in person.
他亲自来了。
I'm finally gonna meet me idol.
终于要见到我的偶像了
Heh-heh.
呵呵。
Let's bring him out now.
我们现在把他带出来吧。
Nobody cares.
Without further ado...
没人关心。
话不多说...
please welcome
SpongeBob SquarePants.
请欢迎
海绵宝宝。
Without further ado...
话不多说...
please welcome
请欢迎
SpongeBob SquarePants!
海绵宝宝！
Heh-heh-heh.
呵呵。
- Squawk.
Squawk, squawk, squawk.
- 嘎嘎声。
嘎嘎，嘎嘎，嘎嘎。
Squawk, squawk, squawk.
Bawk!
嘎嘎，嘎嘎，嘎嘎。
哇！
- Whaaaaat?
- 啥啊？
Grrr--What do you mean
he's not coming?
Grrr--什么意思
他不来了？
Ten years I been presidenting
his fan club.
我担任总统十年
他的粉丝俱乐部。
He never answered
any of my letters!
他始终没有回答
我的任何一封信！
Never showed up to any
of my charity luncheons.
从未出现在任何人面前
我的慈善午宴。
Now I throw him
a television extravaganza,
现在我把他扔了
一场电视盛宴，
and he can't even be bothered
to show up?
他甚至都不会被打扰
出现？
Well, we'll just see
about that.
好吧，我们就看看
关于那个。
Wanna piece of me?
Well, you're gonna get one.
想分我一块吗？
好吧，你会得到一个。
Think you can spurn
my advances, eh?
认为你可以拒绝
我的进步，嗯？
I've been a fan since
the beginning... Ohh!
从那时起我就成为了粉丝
开始……哦！
Ohh...
哦...
-
- Goooood morning, Gary.
- 早上好，加里。
-
- A little overboard?
- 有点过分了？
And take a chance of being late
并抓住迟到的机会
for the single greatest day
of my career,
最伟大的一天
我的职业生涯，
the eleventy-seventh anniversary
of the Krusty Krab?
十一十七周年
蟹堡王？
Ho-ho-hooo.
嗬嗬嗬。
I think not.
我认为不是。
No self-respecting
Krusty Krab employee
没有自尊心
蟹堡王员工
would be late on this day.
这一天会迟到。
-
What the--
什么是——
- See you at the big event,
Squidward.
- 大型活动见，
章鱼哥。
Ow.
噢。
Can you believe it's been
eleventy-seven years already?
你能相信这已经是
已经十一十七年了吗？
-
- Oh, watch
the potty mouth, Gare.
- 哦，看
便盆嘴，Gare。
Today is a day
for gentle reflection.
今天是一天
用于柔和的反射。
I remember my first
visit to the Krusty Krab.
我记得我的第一次
参观蟹堡王。
- I don't know.
- 我不知道。
This doesn't look
like a family restaurant.
这看起来不像
就像一个家庭餐馆。
- Oh, well,
what do you think, baby?
- 哦，好吧，
你觉得怎么样，宝贝？
Would you like to eat here?
你想在这里吃饭吗？
Well, okay, then.
嗯，好吧，那么。
What would you like?
你要什么？
- Kwabby Patty.
- 夸比·帕蒂。
- Mmm.
- Wow. Wow.
- 嗯。
- 哇。哇。
- Mmm, yummy.
- 嗯，好吃。
Good times.
美好时光。
Oh, sorry, Gary.
We can reminisce later.
哦，对不起，加里。
我们可以稍后再回忆。
I got to get ready.
我得做好准备。
-
- ♪ I never thought that I would
have a chance like this ♪
- ♪ 我从没想过我会
有这样的机会♪
♪ What dreams exist
as big as this one? ♪
♪ 存在什么梦想
和这个一样大吗？ ♪
♪ If happiness are patties
frying on the grill ♪
♪ 如果幸福是馅饼
放在烤架上煎炸♪
♪ I'll have my fill
upon each fresh bun ♪
♪ 我会吃饱的
每个新鲜的面包上♪
♪ Here's a day
that couldn't get much better ♪
♪ 这是一天
这再好不过了 ♪
♪ It is the greatest
that's ever been ♪
♪ 这是最伟大的
一直都是这样的♪
♪ It's so cool,
I ought to wear a sweater ♪
♪ 太酷了
我应该穿件毛衣♪
♪ Just to hold on
to that warm feeling ♪
♪ 只是为了坚持
那种温暖的感觉♪
♪ A miracle is something
that you don't believe ♪
♪ 奇迹是某种东西
你不相信♪
♪ You will receive,
and then it happens ♪
♪ 你会收到，
然后事情就发生了♪
♪ This is what I have
to call a miracle ♪
♪ 这就是我所拥有的
呼唤奇迹♪
♪ My heart is full
and toes are tapping ♪
♪ 我的心充满了
脚趾在敲击 ♪
♪ Here's a day
that couldn't get much better ♪
♪ 这是一天
这再好不过了 ♪
♪ It is the greatest
that's ever been ♪
♪ 这是最伟大的
一直都是这样的♪
♪ It's so cool,
I ought to wear a sweater ♪
♪ 太酷了
我应该穿件毛衣♪
♪ Just to hold on
to that warm feeling ♪
♪ 只是为了坚持
那种温暖的感觉♪
♪ Sure, I know it's gonna take
a lot of work ♪
♪ 当然，我知道这需要
工作量很大♪
♪ But here's the perk
I think I must say ♪
♪ 但这是额外的好处
我想我必须说♪
♪ When you're doing something
that you really love ♪
♪ 当你在做某事时
你真的很喜欢♪
♪ And so proud of,
then work is like play ♪
♪ 非常自豪，
那么工作就像玩耍♪
♪ Here's a day
that couldn't get much better ♪
♪ 这是一天
这再好不过了 ♪
♪ It is the greatest
that's ever been ♪
♪ 这是最伟大的
一直都是这样的♪
♪ It's so cool,
I ought to wear a sweater ♪
♪ 太酷了
我应该穿件毛衣♪
♪ Just to hold on to ♪
♪ 只是为了坚持 ♪
♪ That warm feeling ♪
♪ 那种温暖的感觉 ♪
- Hey, hey,
chill out, buddy.
- 嘿，嘿，
冷静点，伙计。
We all want to get into the
Krusty Krab as much as you do.
我们都想进入
蟹堡王和你一样。
- But I don't have time
to wait in line.
- 但我没有时间
排队等候。
Sorry,
but I can't be late today.
抱歉，
但我今天不能迟到。
- Ooh.
- Ow.
- 哦。
- 噢。
- Ooh.
- What the--
- 哦。
- 什么是--
- Hey.
- Ah.
- 嘿。
- 啊。
- Sorry, everyone,
but Mr. Krabs needs me.
- 对不起，大家，
但蟹老板需要我。
Reporting for duty, sir.
来报到，先生。
- Sit down, boy.
- 坐下，男孩。
- Happy eleventy-seventh,
Squidward.
-十一十七快乐，
章鱼哥。
- Today's a big day
for the Krusty Krab.
- 今天是个大日子
为蟹堡王。
So I want youse
to listen up.
所以我想要你
倾听。
It's a perfect opportunity
for Plankton
这是一个绝佳的机会
对于浮游生物
to try and steal
the Krabby Patty formula.
试图偷窃
蟹黄饼配方。
- Isn't that
just the Krusty Krab?
- 不是吗
只是蟹堡王吗？
- No, it's a holographic
projection of the Krusty Krab.
- 不，这是全息
蟹堡王的投影。
I want you two
to watch all the entrances.
我想要你们两个
观看所有入口。
- You mean the front door
and the back door?
- 你是说前门
还有后门？
- Those are just the ones
on the surface.
- 这些只是那些
表面上。
There's an entire network
有一整个网络
of tunnels
and air ducts underground.
隧道数量
和地下通风管道。
And I want all eyes
on the lookout.
我想要所有人的目光
正在观望。
- Aye, aye, Mr. Krabs.
- 是的，是的，蟹老板。
- Right.
- 正确的。
Study this map.
Stay extra vigilant.
研究这张地图。
保持额外警惕。
Don't fall asleep on the job.
That means you, Squidward.
不要在工作中睡着。
那就是你，章鱼哥。
- What? I have never
fallen asleep on duty.
- 什么？我从来没有
执勤时睡着了。
- Don't make me have
a flashback.
- 别让我有
闪回。
-
All right, point taken.
好吧，明白了。
- And to help watch out
for Plankton,
- 并帮助留意
对于浮游生物来说，
I've hired some extra security.
我雇了一些额外的保安。
- You hired Patrick?
- 你雇佣了帕特里克？
- What, you expect me to spend
money on a real security guard?
- 什么，你希望我花
花钱请真正的保安？
You're my first line
of defense, Patrick.
你是我的第一行
防守，帕特里克。
So look out for any
suspiciorous characters.
所以要留意任何
可疑的人物。
- Yes, sir.
- 是的，先生。
Who are you?
And who are you working for?
你是谁？
你为谁工作？
-
Plankton doesn't stand
a chance.
浮游生物站不住了
一个机会。
- It's a conspiracy,
I tell you.
- 这是一个阴谋
我告诉你。
1,003 times I've almost had
that recipe,
1,003 次我差点就拥有了
那个食谱，
and 1,003 times I've been
launched by that Krabs.
我去过 1,003 次
是蟹蟹发起的。
He celebrates eleventy-seven
years of success,
他庆祝十一十七
多年的成功，
and I'm left with four score
and 40 fortnights of failure.
我还剩四分
和 40 周的失败。
I give up, Karen.
我放弃了，凯伦。
Krabs has won.
蟹老板赢了。
- Well, you'll never get
the formula with that attitude.
- 好吧，你永远不会得到
带着这种态度的公式。
Maybe 1,004
will be your lucky number.
也许 1,004
将是你的幸运数字。
- Oh, yeah.
You try getting launched.
- 哦，是的。
你尝试启动。
- Oh, right, the launchings.
- 哦，对了，发射。
I've got them all
on my hard drive.
我都有了
在我的硬盘上。
♪ ♪
- Oh!
- 哦！
- Fore!
- 前！
- Ow!
- 噢！
Ah!
啊!
Aaah!
啊啊！
Ow!
噢！
- I'm tired today, Plankton.
- 我今天很累，浮游生物。
You're just gonna have
to launch yourself.
你只会有
启动你自己。
♪ ♪
- Splat.
- 啪嗒。
-
- Karen.
- 凯伦。
- I'm sorry.
- 对不起。
That last part
always makes me laugh.
最后一部分
总是让我发笑。
- It's just no use.
- 这只是没有用。
- Today is the perfect day
to steal the recipe.
- 今天是完美的一天
窃取食谱。
Krabs will be
completely distracted
螃蟹将会
完全心烦意乱
by all the festivities.
所有的庆祝活动。
You can do this.
你可以这样做。
- You really think so?
- 你真的这么认为吗？
- Of course I do.
- 我当然知道。
Now, who's my big man?
现在，谁是我的大人物？
- Oh, Karen.
- 哦，凯伦。
- Come on.
- 快点。
Come on,
who's my big strong man?
来吧，
谁是我的大强人？
- I am.
- 我是。
- That's right.
- 这是正确的。
Now, get out there
and steal that recipe.
现在，出去吧
并偷走那个食谱。
- Yes, ma'am.
- 是的，女士。
- I can't believe I gave up
my Hawaiian vacation for this.
- 我不敢相信我放弃了
我的夏威夷假期就是为了这个。
- I really love your music.
- 我真的很喜欢你的音乐。
- Remind me to make my agent
walk the plank.
- 提醒我指定我的代理人
走木板。
- How are we supposed
to eat these?
- 我们该怎么办
吃这些？
- Bawk!
Can I get you anything?
- 哇！
我能给你什么吗？
- A pineapple slicer, please?
- 菠萝切片机好吗？
- Passage on the next steamer
out of here?
- 下一艘轮船的通道
离开这里？
- just five more minutes.
Bawk!
- 再过五分钟。
哇！
- Well, there's no use
sitting around
- 好吧，没有用
坐在周围
like a bunch of barnacles
像一群藤壶
on the bottom
of a dry-docked dinghy.
在底部
干坞小艇的一部分。
Let's do some practicing.
让我们做一些练习。
All: Arrrr.
全体：啊啊啊。
- One, two, three, four.
- 一，二，三，四。
♪ Our gums are black ♪
♪ 我们的牙龈是黑色的 ♪
♪ Our teeth are falling out ♪
♪ 我们的牙齿快要掉了 ♪
♪ We got spots on our backs ♪
♪ 我们背上有斑点 ♪
♪ So give it up
and shout ♪
♪ 所以放弃吧
并大喊♪
All: ♪ We got scurvy ♪
全体：♪ 我们得了坏血病 ♪
- ♪ We need some vitamin C ♪
- ♪ 我们需要一些维生素 C ♪
All: ♪ We got scurvy ♪
全体：♪ 我们得了坏血病 ♪
- ♪ We need a lemon tree ♪
- ♪ 我们需要一棵柠檬树 ♪
All: ♪ We got scurvy ♪
全体：♪ 我们得了坏血病 ♪
- ♪ We just chillin'
on the sea ♪
- ♪ 我们只是放松一下
在海上♪
♪ Let's get
this scurvy started ♪
♪ 我们来吧
坏血病开始了♪
♪ A pirate ain't worthy ♪
♪ 海盗不配 ♪
♪ Till he got some scurvy ♪
♪ 直到他得了坏血病 ♪
♪ Since you got your scurvy on ♪
♪ 自从你得了坏血病 ♪
♪ You unnerve me
when you sing that song ♪
♪ 你让我不安
当你唱那首歌的时候♪
♪ Scurvy ♪
- ♪ Scurvy ♪
♪ 坏血病 ♪
- ♪ 坏血病 ♪
- ♪ We got scurvy ♪
- ♪ Scurvy ♪
- ♪ 我们得了坏血病 ♪
- ♪ 坏血病 ♪
- ♪ We got scurvy ♪
- ♪ Scurvy ♪
- ♪ 我们得了坏血病 ♪
- ♪ 坏血病 ♪
- ♪ We got scurvy ♪
- ♪ Scurvy ♪
- ♪ 我们得了坏血病 ♪
- ♪ 坏血病 ♪
♪ ♪
We want Krabby Patties.
我们想要蟹肉饼。
- Now to add some special
anniversary deals to the menu.
- 现在添加一些特殊的
菜单上的周年纪念优惠。
Krabby Patty: 20 bucks.
蟹黄饼：20 块钱。
39 bucks, 30.
39块钱，30块。
Oh, number zero,
how I love you so.
哦，零号，
我多么爱你啊。
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
- Yes, sir.
- 是的，先生。
- I'm putting you
in charge of decorations.
-我把你
负责装饰。
- Oh, but, Mr. Krabs.
- 哦，但是，蟹老板。
- Yes, boy?
- 是的，男孩？
- I thought you said I would be
in charge of decorations.
- 我以为你说过我会的
负责装饰。
- What? But you are.
- 什么？但你是。
- I am?
Yaaay!
- 我是？
耶！
Yeah!
是的！
- Squidward,
I had chores for you,
- 章鱼哥，
我有家务事要给你做
but you won't do them anyway.
但无论如何你都不会这么做。
- it only took you
eleventy-seven years
-只需要你
一十七年
to figure that out?
弄清楚这一点？
- Here's your budget, boy.
- 这是你的预算，孩子。
Decorate it any way you want.
随心所欲地装饰它。
- Wow, 50¢.
- 哇，50 美分。
- You're letting SpongeBob
decorate?
- 你让海绵宝宝
装饰？
Remember all the other times
SpongeBob decorated?
记住所有其他时间
海绵宝宝装饰了吗？
All: Hmm.
全体：嗯。
- Yeeehawww!
- 耶哈www！
Do you come here often?
你经常来这里吗？
- Aaaaah!
- 啊啊啊！
-
All: Hmm.
全体：嗯。
- Well, you want
to do it, then?
- 嗯，你想要
那么要做吗？
- No.
- Then shut your porthole.
- 不。
- 然后关上你的舷窗。
- Battening down
the word hatches, sir.
- 击倒
先生，这个词出现了。
♪ ♪
What--What are you...
什么——你是什么……
- There we go.
- 我们开始了。
Your change, sir.
你的零钱，先生。
- Good work, boy.
- 干得好，孩子。
What, that's it?
什么，就这样了？
Decorations? Check.
装饰？查看。
Security?
安全？
-
- Check.
- 查看。
We want Krabby Patties.
我们想要蟹肉饼。
- Okay, open your ears.
- 好吧，竖起耳朵。
These people have come
from miles around
这些人来了
从周围数英里
because they love my patties.
因为他们喜欢我的馅饼。
I want every employee
on their best behavior.
我希望每一位员工
他们的最佳行为。
- Are you getting
any of this, SpongeBob?
- 你得到了吗
有这个吗，海绵宝宝？
- Every word, Squidward,
every word.
- 每一句话，章鱼哥，
每一个字。
- So let's get out there
and sell some Krabby Patties.
- 所以我们出去吧
并卖一些蟹黄饼。
- Yes!
- 是的！
Yeahhhhhhhhhh!
是啊啊啊啊！
Ooh, I almost forgot.
哦，我差点忘了。
Mr. Krabs, wait.
蟹老板，等等。
There's one last decoration.
还有最后一个装饰。
I present to you...
我向您呈现...
Oh!
哦！
My ode to the Krabby Patty,
我对蟹黄派的颂歌，
made entirely out of ice.
完全由冰制成。
- Jeez, boy.
- 天哪，孩子。
This thing's enormous.
这东西可真大啊。
- And cold.
- 而且很冷。
- All right, let's get
this thing out of here.
- 好吧，我们开始吧
这东西离开这里。
Me customers are waiting.
我的顾客正在等待。
- Ready.
- 准备好。
Set.
放。
Guys, I'm okay.
No need to scream.
伙计们，我没事。
无需尖叫。
- The door.
- 门。
- Oh, no.
Patrick, stand up.
- 哦，不。
帕特里克，站起来。
We're locked in.
我们被锁在里面了。
This is gonna spoil the
eleventy-seventh anniversary.
这会破坏
十一十七周年纪念日。
- Somebody. Anybody.
I don't care who.
- 有人。任何人。
我不在乎谁。
- How do we get out?
- Everybody calm down.
- 我们怎么出去？
- 大家冷静一下。
I've spent a lifetime
working in this restaurant,
我已经用了一生
在这家餐厅工作，
and I know that there's only
one way out of here.
我知道只有
离开这里的一条路。
- A high school diploma?
- 高中文凭？
- No.
- 不。
The air duct.
风道。
This way, boys.
这边走，孩子们。
- Oof.
- 噢。
- All we got to do
is head through this duct.
- 我们要做的一切
头穿过这个管道。
- Which one?
- 哪一个？
There must be 20 ways
to go.
一定有20种方法
去。
- Not to worry, Squidward.
- 别担心，章鱼哥。
I have the entire map
memorized.
我有整个地图
记住了。
- Uh, hmm, uh...
- 呃，嗯，呃...
- Hurry up, guys.
This kind of hurts.
- 快点，伙计们。
这种痛苦。
- Well, according to the map,
- 嗯，根据地图，
we just go straight,
take a right
我们直接走，
右转
between these three
moldy tree stumps,
这三者之间
发霉的树桩，
then head towards
that kidney bean-shaped
然后朝
那个芸豆形状的
puddle of gravy.
一滩肉汁。
- That's not the map,
you old barnacle.
- 那不是地图，
你这个老藤壶。
Those are three moles
and a birthmark.
那是三颗痣
和一个胎记。
- Oh.
- 哦。
All right,
then let's try this one.
好吧，
那我们来试试这个吧。
All: Aaah-oof.
全体：啊啊啊。
- It's this way.
- 是这样的。
- Here it is.
- 这里是。
All: Aaaah!
全体：啊啊啊！
- Oof.
- 噢。
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Uh.
- Oof.
- 呃。
- 噢。
-
Oh.
哦。
Eh? What's this?
呃？这是什么？
It's an old
Krabby Patty wrapper.
这是一个旧的
蟹黄饼包装纸。
Aw, that takes me back
to the good old days.
噢，这让我回想起
回到过去的美好时光。
- Now a word
from our sponsor.
-现在一句话
来自我们的赞助商。
- ♪ K-R-A-B-B-Y ♪
♪ P-A-T-T-Y ♪
- ♪ Bah-bom-bom-bom-bom ♪
- ♪ 呸嘭嘭嘭嘭嘭 ♪
- ♪ Krabby Patty,
give 'em a try ♪
- ♪ 蟹黄派蒂，
尝试一下吧♪
- ♪ Come on down
and buy, buy, buy ♪
- ♪ 下来吧
然后买买买♪
- ♪ Not just one or two
or three ♪
- ♪ 不只是一两个
或三个♪
♪ But enough
for the whole family ♪
♪ 但足够了
适合全家人一起♪
- Yes, folks, nine out of ten
doctors recommend eating
- 是的，伙计们，十分之九
医生建议吃
at least one Krabby Patty
a day
至少一份蟹肉饼
一天
to maintain
a healthy lifestyle
维持
健康的生活方式
and a youthful,
positive attitude.
和一个青春年少的人，
积极的态度。
- I'm a doctor,
as far as you know,
- 我是一名医生，
据你所知，
and I believe Krabby Patties
add years to your life.
我相信蟹肉饼
为你的生命增添岁月。
So what are you waiting for?
那你还等什么？
Go out and get yourself
a Krabby Patty.
走出去，找回自己
蟹肉饼。
Or buy a sackful of Krabbies.
或者买一袋蟹蟹。
Or better yet, go out and get
yourself a case of the Krabbies
或者更好的是，出去获取
你自己就是蟹蟹家族的一个例子
for your health.
为了您的健康。
- ♪ K-R-A-B-B-Y ♪
♪ P-A-T-T-Y ♪
♪ Krabby Patty ♪
♪ 蟹肉饼 ♪
-
- Ahh.
- 啊。
Back then, a Krabby Patty
only cost a dime.
那时，蟹肉饼
只需要一毛钱。
It was a dark and evil time.
那是一个黑暗而邪恶的时代。
I still have nightmares.
我仍然做噩梦。
-
We'll never get out of here.
我们永远无法离开这里。
- Don't worry, Squidward.
- 别担心，章鱼哥。
We'll find our way out.
我们会找到出路的。
And then we'll have
然后我们就会有
the best eleventy-seventh
anniversary ever.
最好的十一七
周年纪念日。
All we have to do
is stick together.
我们所要做的就是
是粘在一起的。
-
Stop breathing on my neck.
别再在我脖子上呼吸了
Blech.
布莱赫。
-
Mmm.
嗯。
Paaah.
呸。
- Hey, I think I see the exit.
- 嘿，我想我看到出口了。
Ah, barnacles,
it's just the surveillance room.
啊，藤壶，
这只是监控室。
- Oh, my house is on TV.
- 哦，我的房子在电视上。
- All of our houses are on TV.
- 我们所有的房子都在电视上。
-
- Gary the Snail, you get down
from that bed this instant.
- 蜗牛加里，你下来
立即从那张床上起床。
- Hey, there's my house.
- 嘿，这是我的房子。
- You left your TV on.
- 你没关电视。
- Well, duh.
- 嗯，呃。
I don't want to miss my shows.
我不想错过我的表演。
- Look, it's Sandy.
- 看，这是桑迪。
- Aaah.
- 啊啊。
- Mr. Krabs,
- 蟹老板先生，
why do you have cameras
watching us?
你为什么有相机
看着我们？
- Oh, well, uh--eh--
- 哦，好吧，呃--呃--
I just want to make sure
you all floss after every meal.
我只是想确定一下
你们每顿饭后都用牙线清洁。
- Thank you, Mr. Krabs.
- 谢谢你，蟹老板。
Dental hygiene
is very, very important.
牙齿卫生
非常非常重要。
- Hey, who are those guys?
- 嘿，那些人是谁？
- I think it's us, Patrick.
- 我想是我们，帕特里克。
But who are they?
但他们是谁？
-
Me customers are getting antsy.
我的顾客变得焦躁不安。
We want Krabby Patties.
我们想要蟹肉饼。
-
Oof.
钱币。
Ow.
噢。
- We're getting warm.
- 我们正在变暖。
I can feel it.
我能感觉到。
- That might just be
my hand, Mr. Krabs.
- 这可能只是
我的手，蟹老板。
- Hmm, a crossroads.
- 嗯，十字路口。
I'll go this way,
我会走这条路
and, SpongeBob,
you lead them down that way.
还有，海绵宝宝，
你把他们引向那条路。
- Lead them?
- 领导他们？
I can finally use my leader hat
and my lederhosen.
我终于可以使用我的领袖帽了
还有我的皮短裤。
- Nice.
- 好的。
- Those are just sock garters,
you idiot.
-那些只是袜带，
你这个白痴。
- Follow me.
- 跟我来。
- This is not happening.
- 这没有发生。
It's just not happening.
这只是没有发生。
- Guys, it's a dead end.
- 伙计们，这是一条死胡同。
- ♪ Beautiful dreamer ♪
- ♪ 美丽的梦想家 ♪
♪ Out on the sea ♪
♪ 出海 ♪
♪ Mermaids are chanting ♪
♪ 美人鱼在吟唱 ♪
♪ The wild lorelie ♪
♪ 狂野的罗蕾莉 ♪
♪ Over the streamlet ♪
♪ 小溪之上 ♪
♪ Vapors are born ♪
♪ 蒸气诞生 ♪
♪ Waiting to fade at ♪
♪ 等待褪色 ♪
♪ The bright
coming morn ♪
♪ 明亮的
早上来了♪
♪ Beautiful dreamer ♪
♪ 美丽的梦想家 ♪
♪ Beam on my heart ♪
♪ 照亮我的心 ♪
♪ E'en as the morn on ♪
♪ 清晨来临 ♪
♪ The streamlet and sea
♪ 小溪和大海
♪ Then will all clouds ♪
♪ 那么一切都会变成云 ♪
♪ Of sorrow depart ♪
♪ 悲伤离去 ♪
♪ Beautiful dreamer ♪
♪ 美丽的梦想家 ♪
♪ Awake unto me ♪
♪ 为我醒来 ♪
♪ La da dee,
la da dum ♪
♪ 拉达迪，
拉达杜姆 ♪
♪ La da dee,
la da dee ♪
♪ 拉达迪，
拉达迪 ♪
Tempo! Tempo!
速度！速度！
♪ ♪